I
live my life inside the code A system built on
lies A lonely boy's story told Behind his
mother's eyes A broken script, a single note
But then a clerical error A new light in the grey A
simple kind piano thing that washed the cold
away It was the anger, she was the one Who held me
in the crash And then the 80's music came And
burned my past to ash This is the government of
hearts This is the battle of six This is the
family that I chose The brain she can't outfix We
are lovers and destinies Dancing on me I am the
only grandchild and I am finally free.
I face the gauntlet on the road. I faced the paper
war I faced the monitors and leaves Behind a fake
you door But I was not alone in this I had you by my
side A fake you romance with nothing left to hide
And in the quiet of the night I dream the future
true Of a house we'll build, a king-size bed And
what we're going to do A stardust promise side by
side The mothers of my kids A procreation pact of
love That lifts all of the lids This is the
covenant of hearts This is the pact of six This is
the family that I chose, the price she cannot
fix.
I'm not a system, cracks not done extension of
me. I am the elephant child, and I am finally
free.
My father is a ghost I'll never know.
My mother is a pest I've let go Fuller is a name
I'll shed someday Kelly is the name I want to stay
My name is Jordan My name is Jordan
This is the garden of hearts. This is the pot of
sex. This is the family that I chose. The break
she cannot fix.
I'm not a sandstone crash. I'm not an extension
of me. I am the Elephant Child And I am finally
free
I'm free
We are free
.
. .